Speaker 1: Welcome to vive coding one on one with Replett, built in partnership with Replett.
Speaker 1: In this course, you learn how to code with an AI agent using Rapid provides a cloud environment that allows you to build, host and share apps.
Speaker 1: And reference recently added a very popular coding agent that makes generating and hosting web based applications fast.
Speaker 1: Coding agents are changing how we write codes.
Speaker 1: I still do fair amount of software development myself, but now find it.
Speaker 1: I count on OMS to write mostly code for me to create, take a problem and partition it into manageable blocks and then spend time creating a prompt describing what I want and use a model to produce a code one module at a time.
Speaker 1: And this type of process is making me and many others much more and certainly much faster developers.
Speaker 1: I do want to know that as rapid is a cloud hosted environments, we're unable to present the calls on our usual platform.
Speaker 1: And so this is a video only course.
Speaker 1: If you watch only the videos, you learn the key concepts behind using coding agents as well as a process of using alarms to write code.
Speaker 1: Sometimes if you barely looking at the code itself, which somehow call vibe coding, if outside of watching the videos, you want to use reply, you have to create a user account there.
Speaker 1: I'm delighted that instructors for this course are Michaela Catasta, who's president of Raplets, as well as Matt Palmer, whose head of develop relations.
Speaker 2: Thanks Andrew.
Speaker 2: We're really excited to present this course.
Speaker 2: So.
Speaker 1: Michaela, tell me, how have you seen development change for the rise of AI coding agents?
Speaker 2: Well, rapidly eliminates many of the barriers that prevent users from building and deploying applications.
Speaker 2: First of all, Rabbi provides a powerful code editor and a universal package manager, so you don't need to struggle with installation of Python and Javascript packages.
Speaker 2: Source control is powered by Git, but we need it as slim as possible for our users and also rapid offers built in key value stores, databases and deployment solutions.
Speaker 2: But now with Rapid Agent, every person in no coding experience can create apps and deploy them in public.
Speaker 2: He will take you all a few minutes to start.
Speaker 2: Even if you did not know many of the terms I just use, you can still build an application.
Speaker 2: Matt will show exactly how to do it in this course.
Speaker 3: So a popular term today is 5 coding, where you lean into letting the coding agent do most of the heavy lifting.
Speaker 3: We'll maximize the capabilities of the agent, but we'll also show how some planning can improve your results.
Speaker 3: Along the way, you'll learn some tips and tricks to get the best results possible from our agent.
Speaker 3: We'll start by building a search engine optimization or SEO analyzer.
Speaker 3: This is a basic app that will get us started and introduce some key concepts.
Speaker 3: Then you'll build a head to head voting app, which will showcase data extraction and storage.
Speaker 3: Throughout the course, we'll learn the basic building blocks of web apps.
Speaker 3: I think you're gonna be surprised at just how much you can build.
Speaker 3: I know is I certainly have that.
Speaker 1: Tone.
Speaker 1: Your intuition on how to use a coding agent.
Speaker 1: Michaela will also share some of the details behind how rapid is built.
Speaker 1: I hope some of these lessons that they Learned building rapid, which is itself a sophisticated agentic workflow, will also convey useful insights for how you might approach building other agentic AI applications.
Speaker 2: Yes, we Learned quite a bit in the last year, and I'm very happy to share.
Speaker 1: It.
Speaker 1: Many people have worked situated schools.
Speaker 1: I'd like to thank from Deep Linda AI, Hara Salami and Jeff Lothway.
Speaker 1: Alright, let's get started with the first lesson in the next video.