Speaker 1: In this lesson, we'll refine our National Parks voting app by integrating our complete dataset.
Speaker 1: We'll also add final features with agent and assistant to ensure everything works correct.
Speaker 1: Play.
Speaker 1: Then we'll deploy the application for public use.
Speaker 1: In the last lesson, we built out our park ranking head voting app.
Speaker 1: Here we got all the functionality implemented and we have our parts being stored in a database.
Speaker 1: We kind of got this nice little ranking table here along with our recent votes that are being stored in Postgres.
Speaker 1: Now we're gonna add some additional functionality.
Speaker 1: We're going to understand how this works and then deploy our app.
Speaker 1: But on that last agent running another lie, I kind of zoned out.
Speaker 1: And so I kind of missed, I miss exactly how things are being implemented.
Speaker 1: So what I'm gonna do now is I'm gonna head to assistant and I'm just gonna ask it to help me understand how my projects working.
Speaker 1: Again, you're gonna see the preview refresh as we switch to assistant mode.
Speaker 1: But I see client, I see server and shared, but like, I don't know much about databases or how we implemented our database.
Speaker 1: So I'm just gonna ask assistant, help me understand what frameworks we used for our database, how does it work and how are we managing it.
Speaker 1: Ends again, I think frameworks are important, something I've been emphasizing throughout this course.
Speaker 1: And understanding what we're building is important because as we get into these debugging issues, you need to understand how to solve these problems and how things work in order to solve those problems.
Speaker 1: So assistant basically just gave me a recap of everything agent just built.
Speaker 1: We're using Postgres, which is the main database configured through a connection URL in our environment variables, which we talked about.
Speaker 1: Cool.
Speaker 1: We're using an Orm framework called Drizzle Orm, which is a typescript first Orm.
Speaker 1: I have no idea what that means.
Speaker 1: We're gonna dig into that in a second.
Speaker 1: We're also doing some schema management.
Speaker 1: So we're defining that.
Speaker 1: I can actually look through here.
Speaker 1: Shared schema.
Speaker 1: Okay, cool.
Speaker 1: Like this is defining the parks table and all of the columns there is defining a votes table.
Speaker 1: Need actually walking through our tables.
Speaker 1: And the code base has two storage implementations and in memory implementation.
Speaker 1: So this was like our old dev implementation.
Speaker 1: We could clean that up if we wanted to.
Speaker 1: So could call out and it explains how these things work.
Speaker 1: Now, what was that?
Speaker 1: Did just walk this through?
Speaker 1: I don't really know what an or for m framework is.
Speaker 1: So I'm gonna say what is an Orm framework and why would I use drizzle or?
Speaker 1: This is exactly how I've you Learned to code, how to build with AI and basically everything that I'm showing you today, I just ask a bunch of questions and, you know, assistant uses the latest models.
Speaker 1: We're just asking questions and understanding kind of what's going on.
Speaker 1: So assistance gonna actually tell us here exactly what our RM, who RRM is, object relational mapping is a framework that lets you interact with your database using programming languages, objects, instead of writing raw SQL queries.
Speaker 1: Okay, so we're using objects instead of writing SQL, which is a language for interacting with databases.
Speaker 1: So it's actually telling us some of the benefits types.
Speaker 1: If the schema management query, building scheme validation.
Speaker 1: Okay, maybe I don't know exactly what these things are, but I could keep digging into them.
Speaker 1: So really the goal here is just to help you understand, hey, I don't actually know what this thing is.
Speaker 1: I don't really know what's going on, but I can learn and I can ask AI and I can use that as a way to kind of reinforce the things that I'm building and to keep iterating.
Speaker 1: So just like that, assistant helped us understand how our application worked and maybe even learn a few things about drizzle, about Postgres and some of the tools that we're building with.
Speaker 1: But I've been really impressed.
Speaker 1: I like how this works.
Speaker 1: We have an application where we can vote for parks.
Speaker 1: The parks are recorded in our database and we get our ranking system.
Speaker 1: This is exactly what I wanted and it's really cool.
Speaker 1: It's really interactive.
Speaker 1: We actually pulled the data and these images from Wikipedia.
Speaker 1: So pretty complicated app here of some data manipulation, visualization, how to extract, transform, load type stuff.
Speaker 1: So now we're gonna go ahead, we're gonna deploy this just like last time, Renee's auto scale, we're and approve those settings.
Speaker 1: And this time you'll notice that we have secrets for our database, right?
Speaker 1: So if we're gonna deploy with APIs or external services, we pull those secrets through as well.
Speaker 1: We'll call this one park challenge.
Speaker 1: Think that's available ends.
Speaker 1: We're gonna go down, we're gonna pull it.
Speaker 1: And just like last time, rebel it is going to build this deployment, it's gonna configure everything and promote that to our production environment.
Speaker 1: There's really not much we need to worry about since we built the entire thing out.
Speaker 1: And typically in development, it's really hard not only to recreate your environment in the cloud, but then to add.
Speaker 1: In those external services to add in databases and manage those databases in a separate environment.
Speaker 1: And we do a bunch of other stuff, right?
Speaker 1: And so what we have here is a database that's directly integrated into the environment.
Speaker 1: As we talked about before, our app kind of installed a bunch of stuff for us.
Speaker 1: It ran some Python scripts to import data.
Speaker 1: You know, agent configured this database that embedded into our application.
Speaker 1: And we didn't have to go anywhere.
Speaker 1: We didn't have to go to another tab, we didn't have to set up another account or inn API key.
Speaker 1: We just did it all from right and reply.
Speaker 1: And so the power of building with agent, the power of building with assistant is that we're able to make these applications, these full stack applications that have databases, that have front ends and they have backends and really build complex tooling from one pain.
Speaker 1: That is vibe coding, right?
Speaker 1: We did a lot of planning, we did a lot of discussion about tools and frameworks.
Speaker 1: But for the most part, this looks a lot different from coding or building.
Speaker 1: Otherwise, there's a lot of bugs.
Speaker 1: We're just kind of going by feel with the debugging and we're going by feel with like how we manage context.
Speaker 1: So I'm gonna let this deployment wrap up.
Speaker 1: We'll come back, we'll finish it up, make sure our application works, and we'll move on from there.
Speaker 1: Cool.
Speaker 1: So we deployed our application.
Speaker 1: We get a URL and it's deployed as an auto scale deployment.
Speaker 1: Again, if you want to learn more about that, you can check out our videos or the documentation.
Speaker 1: Opening the app, we get exactly what we had before.
Speaker 1: I can vote on Mammoth Cave.
Speaker 1: And actually, it's important to note that the same scores pulled through from before, that's because we're using the same database.
Speaker 1: So we have our voting system, we have some recent votes, and we have our rankings that are being stored persistently in our database.
Speaker 1: As I kind of talked about, this is the power of ruplet.
Speaker 1: We just deployed this live on the internet for anybody to access.
Speaker 1: If you want to share with your family or friends, you could do just that.
Speaker 1: And yeah, you know, end to end, full stack application, persistent storage, vibe coded all the way.
Speaker 1: So in our next lesson, we're gonna talk about next steps, we're gonna talk about where to go from here.
Speaker 1: But thanks for joining along.
Speaker 1: Thanks for building some cool apps. Let's wrap it up.